//array of objects
export const Questions = [
  {
    
    prompt: "What are the “house words” of House Greyjoy?",
    option1: "Unbowed, Unbent, Unbroken",
    option2: "We Do Not Sow",
    option3: "Ours Is the Fury",
    option4: "Winter Is Coming",
    ans: "B",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "What is the name of the band of assassins that Arya Stark joins in Braavos?",
    option1: "Brotherhood Without Banners",
    option2: "Faceless Men",
    option3: "Second Sons",
    option4: "Sons of the Harpy",
    ans: "B",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "Jamie Lannister has a golden ___.",
    option1: "hand",
    option2: "sword",
    option3: "chariot",
    option4: "dick",
    ans: "A",
  },

  {
    
    prompt: "Which of the following is not a name of one of Daenerys Targaryen's dragons?",
    option1: "Rhaegal",
    option2: "Viserion",
    option3: "Drogon",
    option4: "Balerion",
    ans: "D",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "Which character, also known as the Lightning Lord, gets continually resurrected by Thoros of Myr after he dies?",
    option1: "Beric Dondarrion",
    option2: "BArristan Selmy",
    option3: "Alliser Thorne",
    option4: "Jaqen H'ghar",
    ans: "A",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "How does Gregor (“the Mountain”) Clegane kill Oberyn Martell, the “Red Viper,” in their trial by combat?",
    option1: "crushes his Skull",
    option2: "strangles him",
    option3: "poisons him",
    option4: "cuts his head off",
    ans: "A",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "Who is Jon Snow's mother?",
    option1: "Cersei Lannister",
    option2: "Lysa Arryn",
    option3: "un unnamed prostitute",
    option4: "Lynna Stark",
    ans: "D",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "Who is the youngest of Ned Stark's children?",
    option1: "Arya",
    option2: "Rickon",
    option3: "Sansa",
    option4: "Bran",
    ans: "B",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "Which former ranger of the Night’s Watch led an army of wildlings as the “King-Beyond-the-Wall” ?",
    option1: "Craster",
    option2: "Janos Slynt",
    option3: "Mance Rayder",
    option4: "Tormund Giantsbane",
    ans: "C",
  },
  {
    
    prompt: "What is Davos Seaworth's nickname ?",
    option1: "The Onion Knight",
    option2: "Hot Pie",
    option3: "the Sand Sanke",
    option4: "The Hound",
    ans: "A",
  },
];

 